Perfect.
>> Um, well, Lorenz, uh, I know it's your
your birthday tomorrow, right? So, I
guess happy birthday and and how does
this feel for you a day early?
>> Yeah, man. It feels awesome. Uh, feels
like a blessing, you know. Uh, thank
God, you know, my birthday and the draft
always lines up every year. So, it's a
good early birthday gift.
>> Awesome. How much uh contact did you
have with the uh Saints over the course
of the off season? And u you know is
this a place that you expected to be a
possibility for you?
>> Yeah. Um not uh not a Oh, can you guys
still see me?
>> Uh there you go. We got you.
>> Um yeah, not too much uh communication
throughout the process. Um I'm pretty
sure we met like at the Senior Bowl. Uh
don't remember sitting down at the
combine too much, but uh yeah, not too
many uh communication. Uh and not I
wouldn't say I really expected to get
picked up by the Saints.
I know every team is going to be
different, but when you talk to teams,
what was their vision for you and and
where you'd fit best in the NFL?
>> Yeah. Um, a couple different teams had
different visions. Um, some have uh
corner with nickel, some have safety
with Nicholls, some have safety. Um, so
a couple different teams have different
visions of what they see.
>> Where do you feel like you fit best?
I feel like I can fit anywhere. I feel
like I can play all five positions in
the back field. Uh so if I need to line
up at corner, nickel, or safety, I feel
like I can be ready to go either one.
>> TJ, how did that Senior Bowl experience
go for you to help you put you in this
position?
>> Yeah. No. Uh it really helped me a lot,
especially I got a chance to play nickel
a lot while I was at the Senior Bowl. So
getting that uh experience at like a NFL
level uh it was really awesome and
helped me prepare for uh this stage
where I'm at today.
>> During your time over at Iowa, it seemed
like every year you kind of got better
and more comfortable. What was kind of
that that that final year like for you
and what do you feel like you uh you
achieved there?
>> Yeah. Uh man, it really just uh was
putting in the work every day. uh had
full confidence in the work I put in and
ability I had. So just going into the
season, you know, just wanted to uh
really accomplish being a complete
corner, you know, being in a run game
while also defending each team's best
receiver and making as many plays that I
can on the ball.
>> Now going in the seventh round, like
just to hear your name call, what did
that mean to you? Just
>> Yeah. Yeah. It uh it meant a lot. No
matter what round it was, I knew it was
going to hit me deep because this is a
sport I've been playing all my life. So,
just even hearing my name called today
was a blessing.
>> Everything that was kind of written
about you throughout the pre-draft
process talks about your physicality.
Would you say that that's a a big part
like a hallmark to your game or or is
there another thing that you emphasize?
>> Yeah, I would definitely say that's a a
big part. you know, I feel like I I'm a
competitor, so I I bring that
physicality uh not only in the run game,
but also uh with receivers, uh you know,
pressing at the line, getting hands on.
So, just being a physical player
overall.
>> And are you have you gotten a did you
get any chance to talk with like Saints
defensive staff like guys like uh
Brandon Staley or anybody like that?
>> Uh no sir, not yet.
>> Are you aware of kind of what the the
system looks like? Just going back to
like even Bangio comparisons and things
like that.
>> Uh not too much. Um just slightly, a
little bit, but not too much. So uh
definitely want to get familiar more
with it.
>> So TJ, what's your day been like then
just uh sitting waiting for that call?
>> Yeah, uh really just sitting around with
family, friends, um having some food, uh
just watching a draft, you know, just
patiently waiting for my name to be
called.
You played uh other positions beyond
corner, right? Like coming like coming
up. I mean,
>> yeah. Yeah. Uh play quarterback,
receiver, uh safety, corner, um about
almost everything.
>> Kind of a a dumb question, but just
interested in your perspective, the the
experience playing quarterback and
receiver. Just how does that help you
now as a corner?
>> Yeah, it helps me a lot uh understanding
uh what quarterbacks and receivers like
to do to what they like to show. So, I
feel like I use that for my game on
being on the defensive side, you know,
just picking up cues and stuff that, you
know, somebody that might not play both
ways might not get all the time.
>> Awesome.
>> Thank you, TJ. Happy birthday, man.
Enjoy the day tomorrow.
>> Hey, thank you guys. I appreciate it.